Register of the George Sokolsky Papers, 1916-1962
Hoover Institution Archives
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS WRITTEN FOR OTHERS, 1938-1962
  - Connely, Emmet F., 1941 October 17. Correspondence and typescript (Folder 11)
  - Cunningham, Edwin S. (by Sokolsky?), n.d. Typescript (Folder 12)
  - Dewey, Thomas E., 1942 August 4 - 1948 March 25. Correspondence and nine typescript drafts (Folder 13)
  - Frakenthaler, George, 1948 October 28. Typescript (Folder 14)
  - Garey, Eugene L., 1946 June 27 - 1948 June 12. Correspondence, printed copy, and typescript (Folder 15)
  - Graham, T. G., 1945 April 20. Typescript (Folder 16)
  - Hawkes, Albert, n.d. Three holograph drafts (Folder 17)
  - Hearst, William Randolph, Jr., 1955 January 22 - 1961 September 4. Correspondence and three typescript drafts (Folder 18)
  - Hoover, Herbert, 1938 April 16 - 1962 May 29. Correspondence and thirteen typescript drafts (Folder 19)
  - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1953 January 6 - 1954 November 24. Correspondence and five typescript drafts (Folder 20)
  - Oursler, Fulton, n.d. Typescript (Folder 21)
  - Smith, Earl, 1960 August 26. Holograph notes and two typescript drafts (Folder 22)
  - Spangler, Harrison E., 1943 August 20. Typescript (Folder 23)
  - Taft, Robert A., 1943 June 3. Typescript (Folder 24)
  - Weir, Ernest T., n.d. Typescript (Folder 25)
- ARTICLES AND BROADCAST TRANSCRIPTS, 1936-1962.
  Typescript drafts, correspondence, and printed copies
  - Broadcasts - American Broadcasting Company. Working copies, correspondence, and printed transcripts (Box 137)
    - General (Folder 1)
    - 1948
      - October (Folder 2)
      - November (Folder 3)
      - December (Folder 4)
    - 1949
      - January (Folder 5)
      - February (Folder 6)
      - March (Folder 7)
      - April (Folder 8)
      - May (Folder 9)
      - June (Folder 10)
      - July (Folder 11)
      - August (Folder 12)
      - September (Folder 13)
      - October (Folder 14)
      - November (Folder 15)
      - December (Folder 16)
    - 1950 (Box 138)
      - January (Folder 1)
      - February (Folder 2)
      - March (Folder 3)
      - April (Folder 4)
      - May (Folder 5)
      - June (Folder 6)
      - July (Folder 7)
      - August (Folder 8)
      - September (Folder 9)
      - October (Folder 10)
      - November (Folder 11)
      - December (Folder 12)
    - 1951
      - January (Folder 13)
      - February (Folder 14)
      - March (Folder 15)
      - April (Folder 16)
      - May (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - June (Folder 2)
      - July (Folder 3)
      - August (Folder 4)
      - September (Folder 5)
      - October (Folder 6)
      - November (Folder 7)
      - December (Folder 8)
    - 1952
      - January (Folder 9)
      - February (Folder 10)
      - March (Folder 11)
      - April (Folder 12)
      - May (Folder 13)
      - June (Folder 14)
      - July (Folder 15)
      - August (Folder 16)
      - September (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - October (Folder 2)
      - November (Folder 3)
      - December (Folder 4)
    - 1953
      - January (Folder 5)
      - February (Folder 6)
      - March (Folder 7)
      - April (Folder 8)
      - May (Folder 9)
      - June (Folder 10)
      - July (Folder 11)
      - August (Folder 12)
      - September (Folder 13)
      - October (Folder 14)
      - November (Folder 15)
      - December (Folder 16)
    - 1954 (Box 141)
      - January (Folder 1)
      - February (Folder 2)
      - March (Folder 3)
      - April (Folder 4)
      - May (Folder 5)
      - June (Folder 6)
      - July (Folder 7)
      - August (Folder 8)
      - September (Folder 9)
      - October (Folder 10)
      - November (Folder 11)
      - December (Folder 12)
    - 1955
      - January (Folder 13)
      - February (Folder 14)
      - March (Folder 15)
      - April (Folder 16)
      - May (Box 142, Folder 1)
      - June (Folder 2)
      - July (Folder 3)
      - August (Folder 4)
      - September (Folder 5)
      - October (Folder 6)
      - November (Folder 7)
      - December (Folder 8)
    - 1956
      - January (Folder 9)
      - April (Folder 10)
      - May (Folder 11)
      - June (Folder 12)
      - July (Folder 13)
      - August (Folder 14)
      - September (Folder 15)
      - October (Folder 16)
      - November (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - December (Folder 2)
    - 1957
      - January (Folder 3)
      - February (Folder 4)
      - March (Folder 5)
      - April (Folder 6)
      - May (Folder 7)
      - June (Folder 8)
      - July (Folder 9)
      - August (Folder 10)
      - September (Folder 11)
      - October (Folder 12)
      - November (Folder 13)
      - December (Folder 14)
    - 1958
      - January (Folder 15)
      - February (Folder 16)
      - March (Box 144, Folder 1)
      - April (Folder 2)
      - May (Folder 3)
      - June (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
      - September (Folder 7)
      - October (Folder 8)
      - November (Folder 9)
    - 1959
      - January (Folder 10)
      - February (Folder 11)
      - March (Folder 12)
      - April (Folder 13)
      - May (Folder 14)
      - June (Folder 15)
      - July (Folder 16)
      - August (Box 145, Folder 1)
      - September (Folder 2)
      - October (Folder 3)
      - November (Folder 4)
      - December (Folder 5)
    - 1960
      - January (Folder 6)
      - February (Folder 7)
      - March (Folder 8)
      - April (Folder 9)
      - May (Folder 10)
      - June (Folder 11)
      - July (Folder 12)
      - August (Folder 13)
      - September (Folder 14)
      - October (Folder 15)
      - November (Folder 16)
      - December (Folder 17)
    - 1961 (Box 146)
      - January (Folder 1)
      - February (Folder 2)
      - March (Folder 3)
      - April (Folder 4)
      - May (Folder 5)
      - June (Folder 6)
      - July (Folder 7)
      - August (Folder 8)
      - September (Folder 9)
      - October (Folder 10)
  - Newspaper columns and editorials. Notes, correspondence, printed material, and typescript drafts (Box 147)
    - Daily Mirror
      - 1946
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May (Folder 5)
        - June (Folder 6)
        - July (Folder 7)
        - August (Folder 8)
        - September (Folder 9)
        - October (Folder 10)
        - November (Folder 11)
        - December (Folder 12)
      - 1947
        - January (Folder 13)
        - February (Folder 14)
        - March (Box 148, Folder 1)
        - April (Folder 2)
        - May (Folder 3)
        - June (Folder 4)
        - July (Folder 5)
        - August (Folder 6)
        - September (Folder 7)
        - October (Folder 8)
        - November (Folder 9)
        - December (Folder 10)
      - 1948
        - January (Folder 11)
        - February (Folder 12)
        - March (Folder 13)
        - April (Folder 14)
        - May (Folder 15)
        - June (Folder 16)
        - July (Box 149, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Folder 4)
        - November (Folder 5)
        - December (Folder 6)
      - 1949
        - January (Folder 7)
        - February (Folder 8)
        - March (Box 150, Folder 1)
        - April (Folder 2)
        - May (Folder 3)
        - June (Folder 4)
        - July (Folder 5)
        - August (Folder 6)
        - September (Folder 7)
        - October (Folder 8)
        - November (Box 151, Folder 1)
        - December (Folder 2)
      - 1950
        - January (Folder 3)
        - February (Folder 4)
        - March (Folder 5)
        - April (Folder 6)
        - May (Folder 7)
        - June (Box 152, Folder 1)
        - July (Folder 2)
        - August (Folder 3)
        - September (Folder 4)
        - October (Folder 5)
        - November (Folder 6)
        - December (Folder 7)
      - 1951
        - January (Folder 8)
        - February (Box 153, Folder 1)
        - March (Folder 2)
        - April (Folder 3)
        - May (Folder 4)
        - June (Folder 5)
        - July (Folder 6)
        - August (Folder 7)
        - September (Folder 8)
        - October (Box 154, Folder 1)
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
      - 1952
        - January (Folder 4)
        - February (Folder 5)
        - March (Folder 6)
        - April (Folder 7)
        - May (Box 155, Folder 1)
        - June (Folder 2)
        - July (Folder 3)
        - August (Folder 4)
        - September (Folder 5)
        - October (Folder 6)
        - November (Folder 7)
        - December (Folder 8)
      - 1953 (Box 156)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May (Folder 5)
        - June (Folder 6)
        - July (Folder 7)
        - August (Folder 8)
        - September (Box 157, Folder 1)
        - October (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
      - 1954
        - January (Folder 5)
        - February (Folder 6)
        - March (Folder 7)
        - April (Folder 8)
        - May (Box 158, Folder 1)
        - June (Folder 2)
        - July (Folder 3)
        - August (Folder 4)
        - September (Folder 5)
        - October (Folder 6)
        - November (Folder 7)
        - December (Box 159, Folder 1)
      - 1955
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February (Folder 3)
        - March (Folder 4)
        - April (Folder 5)
        - May (Folder 6)
        - June (Folder 7)
        - July (Folder 8)
        - August (Folder 9)
        - September (Folder 10)
        - October (Box 160, Folder 1)
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
      - 1956
        - January (Folder 4)
        - February (Folder 5)
        - March (Folder 6)
        - April (Folder 7)
        - May (Folder 8)
        - June (Folder 9)
        - July (Box 161, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Folder 4)
        - November (Folder 5)
        - December (Folder 6)
      - 1957
        - January (Folder 7)
        - February (Folder 8)
        - March (Box 162, Folder 1)
        - April (Folder 2)
        - May (Folder 3)
        - June (Folder 4)
        - July (Folder 5)
        - August (Folder 6)
        - September (Folder 7)
        - October (Folder 8)
        - November (Folder 9)
        - December (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - 1958
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February (Folder 3)
        - March (Folder 4)
        - April (Folder 5)
        - May (Folder 6)
        - June (Folder 7)
        - July (Folder 8)
        - August (Folder 9)
        - September (Folder 10)
        - October (Box 164, Folder 1)
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
      - 1959
        - January (Folder 4)
        - February (Folder 5)
        - March (Folder 6)
        - April (Folder 7)
        - May (Folder 8)
        - June (Folder 9)
        - July (Folder 10)
        - August (Folder 11)
        - September (Box 165, Folder 1)
        - October (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
      - 1960
        - January (Folder 5)
        - February (Folder 6)
        - March (Folder 7)
        - April (Folder 8)
        - May (Folder 9)
        - June (Folder 10)
        - July (Box 166, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Folder 4)
        - November (Folder 5)
        - December (Folder 6)
      - 1961
        - January (Folder 7)
        - February (Folder 8)
        - March (Folder 9)
        - April (Box 167, Folder 1)
        - May (Folder 2)
        - June (Folder 3)
        - July (Folder 4)
        - August (Folder 5)
        - September (Folder 6)
        - October (Folder 7)
        - November (Folder 8)
        - December (Folder 9)
      - 1962 (Box 168)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May (Folder 5)
        - June (Folder 6)
        - July (Folder 7)
        - August (Folder 8)
        - September (Box 169, Folder 1)
        - October (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
    - King Features
      - 1950
        - January (Folder 5)
        - February (Folder 6)
        - March (Box 170)
          - 1-15 (Folder 1)
          - 16-31 (Folder 2)
        - April (Folder 3)
        - May
          - 1-15 (Folder 4)
          - 16-31 (Box 171, Folder 1)
        - June
          - 1-15 (Folder 2)
          - 16-30 (Folder 3)
        - July
          - 1-15 (Folder 4)
          - 16-31 (Folder 5)
        - August (Box 172, Folder 1)
        - September (Folder 2)
        - October
          - 1-15 (Folder 3)
          - 16-31 (Folder 4)
        - November (Box 173, Folder 1)
        - December (Folder 2)
      - 1951
        - January (Folder 3)
        - February (Box 174, Folder 1)
        - March
          - 1-15 (Folder 2)
          - 16-31 (Folder 3)
        - April
          - 1-15 (Folder 4)
          - 16-30 (Box 175, Folder 1)
        - May (Folder 2)
        - June
          - 1-15 (Folder 3)
          - 16-30 (Folder 4)
        - July (Box 176, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Box 177, Folder 1)
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
      - 1952 (Box 178)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Box 179, Folder 1)
        - May (Folder 2)
        - June
          - 1-15 (Folder 3)
          - 16-30 (Box 180, Folder 1)
        - July
          - 1-15 (Folder 2)
          - 16-31 (Folder 3)
        - August (Folder 4)
        - September (Folder 5)
        - October (Box 181)
          - 1-15 (Folder 1)
          - 16-30 (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
      - 1953 (Box 182)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Box 183, Folder 1)
        - May
          - 1-15 (Folder 2)
          - 16-31 (Folder 3)
        - June (Folder 4)
        - July (Box 184, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September
          - 1-15 (Folder 3)
          - 16-30 (Folder 4)
        - October (Box 185, Folder 1)
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
      - 1954 (Box 186)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Box 187, Folder 1)
        - May (Folder 2)
        - June (Folder 3)
        - July (Box 188)
          - 1-15 (Folder 1)
          - 16-31 (Folder 2)
        - August (Folder 3)
        - September (Folder 4)
        - October (Box 189, Folder 1)
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
      - 1955
        - January (Folder 4)
        - February (Box 190, Folder 1)
        - March (Folder 2)
        - April (Folder 3)
        - May (Folder 4)
        - June (Box 191, Folder 1)
        - July (Folder 2)
        - August (Folder 3)
        - September (Box 192, Folder 1)
        - October (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
      - 1956 (Box 193)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May (Box 194, Folder 1)
        - June (Folder 2)
        - July (Folder 3)
        - August (Folder 4)
        - September (Box 195, Folder 1)
        - October (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
      - 1957 (Box 196)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May (Box 197, Folder 1)
        - June (Folder 2)
        - July
          - 1-15 (Folder 3)
          - 16-31 (Folder 4)
        - August (Box 198, Folder 1)
        - September (Folder 2)
        - October (Folder 3)
        - November (Box 199, Folder 1)
        - December (Folder 2)
      - 1958
        - January (Folder 3)
        - February (Box 200, Folder 1)
        - March (Folder 2)
        - April (Folder 3)
        - May (Box 201, Folder 1)
        - June (Folder 2)
        - July (Folder 3)
        - August (Box 202, Folder 1)
        - September (Folder 2)
        - October (Folder 3)
        - November (Folder 4)
        - December (Box 203, Folder 1)
      - 1959
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February (Folder 3)
        - March (Folder 4)
        - April (Folder 5)
        - May (Box 204, Folder 1)
        - June (Folder 2)
        - July (Folder 3)
        - August (Box 205, Folder 1)
        - September (Folder 2)
        - October (Folder 3)
        - November (Box 206, Folder 1)
        - December (Folder 2)
      - 1960
        - January (Folder 3)
        - February (Folder 4)
        - March (Box 207, Folder 1)
        - April (Folder 2)
        - May
          - 1-15 (Folder 3)
          - 16-31 (Folder 4)
        - June (Box 208, Folder 1)
        - July (Folder 2)
        - August
          - 1-15 (Folder 3)
          - 16-31 (Folder 4)
        - September (Box 209, Folder 1)
        - October
          - 1-15 (Folder 2)
          - 16-31 (Folder 3)
        - November (Folder 4)
        - December (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - 1961
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February (Folder 3)
        - March (Box 211, Folder 1)
        - April (Folder 2)
        - May (Folder 3)
        - June (Box 212, Folder 1)
        - July (Folder 2)
        - August (Folder 3)
        - September (Box 213, Folder 1)
        - October (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
      - 1962 (Box 214)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March
          - 1-15 (Folder 3)
          - 16-31 (Folder 4)
        - April (Box 215, Folder 1)
        - May
          - 1-15 (Folder 2)
          - 16-31 (Folder 3)
        - June (Folder 4)
        - July (Box 216, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Box 217, Folder 1)
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
    - New York Herald Tribune (Box 218)
      - General (Folder 1-3)
      - 1936
        - March (Folder 4)
        - April (Folder 5)
        - May (Folder 6)
        - June (Folder 7)
        - July (Folder 8)
        - August (Box 219, Folder 1)
        - September (Folder 2)
        - October (Folder 3)
        - November (Folder 4)
        - December (Folder 5)
      - 1937
        - January (Folder 6)
        - February (Folder 7)
        - March (Folder 8)
        - April (Folder 9)
        - May (Folder 10)
        - June (Folder 11)
        - July (Folder 12)
        - August (Folder 13)
        - September (Folder 14)
        - October (Folder 15)
        - November (Folder 16)
        - December (Folder 17)
      - 1938
        - January (Folder 18)
        - May (Folder 19)
        - August (Folder 20)
        - November (Folder 21)
      - 1939
        - January (Folder 22)
        - April (Folder 23)
        - July (Folder 24)
        - September (Folder 25)
        - October (Folder 26)
      - 1940
        - Jan (Folder 27)
        - February (Folder 28)
        - April (Folder 29)
        - June (Folder 30)
    - New York Journal American, 1950 January (Folder 31)
    - The Sun (New York) (Box 220)
      - 1940
        - July (Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Folder 4)
        - November (Folder 5)
        - December (Folder 6)
      - 1941
        - January (Folder 7)
        - February (Folder 8)
        - March (Folder 9)
        - April (Folder 10)
        - May (Folder 11)
        - June (Folder 12)
        - July (Box 221, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Folder 4)
        - November (Folder 5)
        - December (Folder 6)
      - 1942
        - January (Folder 7)
        - February (Folder 8)
        - March (Box 222, Folder 1)
        - April (Folder 2)
        - May (Folder 3)
        - June (Folder 4)
        - July (Folder 5)
        - August (Folder 6)
        - September (Box 223, Folder 1)
        - October (Folder 2)
        - November (Folder 3)
        - December (Folder 4)
      - 1943
        - January (Folder 5)
        - February (Folder 6)
        - March (Folder 7)
        - April (Box 224, Folder 1)
        - May (Folder 2)
        - June (Folder 3)
        - July (Folder 4)
        - August (Folder 5)
        - September (Folder 6)
        - October (Folder 7)
        - November (Box 225, Folder 1)
        - December (Folder 2)
      - 1944
        - January (Folder 3)
        - February (Folder 4)
        - March (Folder 5)
        - April (Folder 6)
        - May (Box 226, Folder 1)
        - June (Folder 2)
        - July (Folder 3)
        - August (Folder 4)
        - September (Folder 5)
        - October (Folder 6)
        - November (Folder 7)
        - December (Box 227, Folder 1)
      - 1945
        - January (Folder 2)
        - February (Folder 3)
        - March (Folder 4)
        - April (Folder 5)
        - May (Folder 6)
        - June (Folder 7)
        - July (Box 228, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Folder 4)
        - November (Folder 5)
        - December (Folder 6)
      - 1946 (Box 229)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May (Folder 5)
        - June (Folder 6)
        - July (Folder 7)
        - August (Box 230, Folder 1)
        - September (Folder 2)
        - October (Folder 3)
        - November (Folder 4)
        - December (Folder 5)
      - 1947 (Box 231)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May (Folder 5)
        - June (Folder 6)
        - July (Box 232, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Folder 4)
        - November (Folder 5)
        - December (Folder 6)
      - 1948 (Box 233)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May (Folder 5)
        - June (Folder 6)
        - July (Box 234, Folder 1)
        - August (Folder 2)
        - September (Folder 3)
        - October (Folder 4)
        - November (Folder 5)
        - December (Folder 6)
      - 1949 (Box 235)
        - January (Folder 1)
        - February (Folder 2)
        - March (Folder 3)
        - April (Folder 4)
        - May (Folder 5)
        - June (Box 236, Folder 1)
        - July (Folder 2)
        - August (Folder 3)
        - September (Folder 4)
        - October (Box 237, Folder 1)
        - November (Folder 2)
        - December (Folder 3)
      - 1950
        - January (Folder 4)
        - February (Folder 5)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1918-1962.
  Clippings, correspondence, memoranda, notes, printed matter, typescript drafts, and reports
  - Acheson, Dean (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Advertising (Folder 2)
  - Africa (Folder 3)
  - Afro-Americans (Folder 4)
  - Airlines - United States (Folder 5)
  - Alaska (Folder 6)
  - Allen, Daniel I. (Folder 7)
  - Amerasia. Includes material on the Institute of Pacific Relations (Folder 8)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Musicians (Folder 10)
  - American Forum for Socialist Education (Folder 11)
  - American Intelligence Agency (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - American Jewish League (Folder 2)
  - American Jewish League Against Communism (Folder 3)
  - American Platform Guild (Folder 4)
  - American-Soviet Science Society (Folder 5)
  - Anderson, Roy. Memoranda written by Anderson in China under various pseudonyms (Folder 6)
  - Anticommunism. Includes material on Circuit Riders, Inc., For America, and Moral Re-Armament (Folder 7-8)